[Theme song]
[Meaningful music]
[Vincenzo’s heavy breathing]
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
[Laugh together]
[Rattling the gold]
[Rough breathing]
Finally today
I see this
I can't believe it when I see it
This is all gold
[Laugh together]
There are also things like cultural assets, right?
[laughter]
[Harsh moaning]
[The gun is fully loaded]
[nervous music]
Thank you for your hard work, lawyer.
That's a harsh price for friendship.
If you stay still until I leave
I won't harm you
Why is this happening?
I can't tell you
I only have one gold bar
Just take it with you
[Rattling gold bars]
[Emphasized sound effect]
Because of just one gold bar
Are you doing this?
[Vincenzo laughs]
(President Cho)
Step back!
After I'm all the way up
Come up with me then.
[Meaningful music]
You're not going to go out and close the door, are you?
I said it won't hurt you
[laughter]
[Picking up the gold bar]
Can I get one too as a souvenir?
[Music that heightens the mood]
[Vincenzo’s groans of difficulty]
[Meaningful music]
[groans with difficulty]
[Vincenzo’s groans of difficulty]
[Vincenzo’s elasticity]
(Vincenzo)
Oh, this thing is really heavy?
[laughter]
Please stay still until I leave.
If you chase me, I will shoot you.
(Vincenzo)
yes
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
But
Why go out with just one?
I just need one
Ah
Boy, it must be heavy.
Couldn’t you have just removed the guillotine file?
How...
[laughter]
[nervous music]
(Vincenzo)
Baby, because of that
By my side until now
It was stuck.
(President Cho)
don't come near
(Vincenzo)
But
Do you think there's a file in there?
huh?
[President Cho’s powerful moans]
[Vincenzo’s groans of difficulty]
[President Cho’s spirit]
[Vincenzo’s powerful moans]
[President Cho’s groans of difficulty]
[Rough breathing]
[breathes and then exhales]
[laughter]
[President Cho’s heavy breathing]
[sigh]
(Junwoo)
Now
Babel Tower Signature
Starting from the 120th and 121st floors
Not one floor, but two floors
It's only for one person
[Meaningful music]
please move my heart
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
It's me
(Junwoo)
Yeah, talk to me.
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
As you all know
A series of lawsuits related to Babel
Isn't it scheduled to proceed?
It's something I have to cover.
Why?
For the health of Babel!
Datz Lite
[President Kim’s urgent groan]
(Junwoo)
Yeah
(President Kim)
Construction of Taishan and Zhongshan new towns
Babel Construction will become a leading company.
I am the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure and Transport, the ruling and opposition parties.
all can move
(Junwoo)
Can You Feel My Heartbeat
[Junwoo’s powerful moans]
Are you so excited?
Yeah
As you know, Korean opinion
Leading is
Isn’t this our Daechang Ilbo?
Babel is in the media at least
You won't be criticized
Okay
(Junwoo)
Not just the tower
We will also guarantee Babel advertisements in Daechang Ilbo.
[laughter]
[The door clicks open]
[Approaching footsteps]
(Junwoo)
What is it?
who?
(Director Tae)
Oh, sorry I'm late.
I suddenly had an urgent meeting.
Foreign Security Intelligence Service International Crime Countermeasures Directorate
This is Director Tae Jong-gu.
[Music that heightens the mood]
welcome
[laughter]
No, not even a single bullet in the magazine.
Why didn’t you bring it in?
[sigh]
[laughter]
(Vincenzo)
True
I think you still consider me a friend
As a friend, let me ask you one question.
Where do you really belong?
[Meaningful music]
Foreign Security Intelligence Service National Security Management Team
This is Agent Black.
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
[Blows out air]
Looking for the guillotine file
Are you intentionally pretending to quit?
Disguised as an industrial spy
I approached President Wang.
Right?
(President Cho)
yes
What about me?
[Meaningful music]
When I met the lawyer
It was really a coincidence
(President Cho)
When I almost died in Italy
Because the lawyer saved me.
(Vincenzo)
um
Boss Wang’s death wasn’t a coincidence, right?
[sigh]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Wang Xiaolin clears his throat]
[Refreshing moan]
[Wang Xiaolin speaks in Chinese]
[Chinese]
Please
[President Cho answers in Chinese]
This bastard…
you are amazing
[Wang Xiaolin's labored groans]
[Machine operating sound]
(President Cho)
Call an ambulance quickly, quickly!
[laughter]
[Elasticity]
[Korean]
No, I didn't see it that way.
Our boss Joe
Are you really a scary person?
[Meaningful music]
Yeah, I'm not that good of a guy.
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
That you're lying to me
I knew it from the beginning
(Vincenzo)
President Wang has eye data.
Hangzhou Wang President Museum
I looked into it and found that there was no such museum.
[laughter]
[hits the floor]
When I left the Chinese office
Why didn’t you bring it up then?
At that time, President Wang’s eye data
It was when I couldn't secure it.
yet
When I was planning a plan.
No, then just keep it blank.
Why did you let this pharmacist come in?
I think it would be more dangerous if I left it empty.
(President Cho)
Does anyone know of the existence of this place?
Maybe there is
(Hongsik)
Has anyone seen that before?
When starting the car
With the old building owner
Meeting with lawyer Vincenzo?
(Larry Kang)
Huh? I saw it too
(Toto)
Uh, me too
He came out from the other side together.
Well, I'm just thinking about it at this point.
It's a reasonable idea, though.
No, let us all go
(Hongsik)
Why do you two meet?
(Chayoung)
Ah, you two today
You have an appointment, yes.
(Heesu)
No, I wear sunglasses too
They say they don’t want to see it.
It's a bit questionable
[Heesu’s laughter]
(Seokdo)
Well then, just the two of us secretly
Do you think you might find some gold?
[Seokdo blows air]
[Meaningful music]
Hey, don't show me such a straight face
I just threw it away
Boy, really
(Cheolwook)
Don't be suspicious
You trust our lawyer, right?
(Yeonjin)
Are you two in the Babel Group?
So that I can't have gold
Aren't you looking for it first?
(Joosung)
Uh, everyone
I think you're too sensitive.
(Kiseok)
Yes, let's go and have fun.
Well, shall we have a singing contest?
- (Chayoung) Oh, good.
- (Kiseok) Yes
(Chayoung)
Ah, one, ah, two
Ah, one, two, three, yeah
(Seokdo)
Well, in one photo
It's also strange that the prize money was 20 million won.
[Seokdo blows air]
[Meaningful music]
Why again?
[Siren sounds]
Boy, I can’t say anything, really.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Vincenzo)
guillotine file
[Vincenzo clicks his lighter]
You didn't plan on giving it to foreign security intelligence, right?
You haven't even seen it yet?
[sigh]
If I had reported it, they would have already come rushing in.
They must have opened the secret room and taken it out.
Why didn't you report it?
Do you want to do business with someone else?
[laughter]
Well, well
That would be more profitable, right?
Who were you trying to do business with?
I haven't decided yet
But the existence of this file
How did you know?
To me, the source of information is
Because it’s not just the boss.
[Meaningful music]
(Hongsik)
What should I do first, what should I do first?
What should I do first?
[Noisy]
(Cheolwook)
Don't run!
[Chayoung's urgent groan]
(Joosung)
Lawyer!
(Cheolwook)
Don't run!
[Seokdo’s sigh]
Everyone because of gold
I feel like I'm in a lot of trouble
That's right
Greed is a trumpet that brings pain
(Seokdo)
It's because they're so frivolous
Ana, really, we
When Geum Gwang-jin comes,
It's just a one-stop solution.
[Yeonjin’s urgent moans]
(Heesu)
You go up, I go down
[Yeonjin speaks]
(Cheolwook)
Ah…
(Yeonjin)
Honey, come quickly!
(Cheolwook)
Don't run, you'll get hurt
[cell phone vibrating sound]
yes
(Chayoung)
Oh, why aren't you answering the phone?
Oh, what's going on?
(Chayoung)
They're back in People Plaza now.
Going down to the basement
[Exciting music]
(President Cho)
What's going on?
(Vincenzo)
Ah, hey, the people are back
[President Cho groans in frustration]
Shhh
Put it in quickly, put it in this secret room quickly.
Chi, chi, chi, I have to clean it up
(President Cho)
No, my clothes...
(Vincenzo)
Why did you put that on your pants?
(Cheolwook)
This is my body's top speed
How can you go faster than this?
(Yeonjin)
Sister, are you over there?
(Heesu)
No, I don't think it's this way.
To go further down, to Nanyaksa Temple
(Yeonjin)
Are you a pharmacist?
[You can hear people talking]
(Vincenzo)
Wait!
(President Cho)
Why?
- (Vincenzo) Gold
- (President Cho) What kind of gold?
Gold, gold, gold, gold, gold!
There, there, there, there
There, there, there!
Hold on tight, hold on tight, hold on tight, hold on tight!
[Gold bar falls]
[The door slams shut]
(Kiseok)
Master!
no
(Toto)
Wait, wait, wait, wait
- (Toto) The director is here
- (Kiseok) Master
(Kiseok)
Huh?
[Larry Kang's urgent moans]
[Kiseok’s sigh]
[breathes and then exhales]
Mr. Lee
[Vincenzo’s groans in pain]
[President Cho’s powerful moans]
[President Cho groans in surprise]
[Vincenzo’s groans in pain]
(in advance)
Boss, what can you possibly have here?
(Hongsik)
Now that I think about it,
I don't know if we've ever found one like this
This is where the bonanza explodes.
[Vincenzo’s powerful moans]
[Vincenzo and President Cho’s harsh moans]
[President Cho groans in surprise]
(Chayoung)
Boss!
(Joosung)
[Chayoung’s heavy breathing]
What do you want?
Why did you follow me here?
I have something important to tell you.
What's so important?
A long time ago, my father
I think you've said it before.
That's where the gold is
[Interesting music]
- Really?
- (Hongsik) Where is that?
tell me
(Chayoung)
That's where...
(Vincenzo)
One more, one more
Where should it be?
(Hongsik)
Ah!
Oh, speak quickly, please.
In our hearts
(Joosung)
I heard it too
[humorous music]
Uh, the most precious treasure is
It's in our hearts
What kind of ghost is being washed away?
Are you trying to distract us now?
[Chayoung’s moans of denial]
No
(Chayoung)
Place your hand on your heart and feel it
(President Cho)
There, there, there
[A clicking sound rings out]
(Joosung)
Crack!
[Meaningful music]
What are you talking about?
(Chayoung)
Huh? no…
Who do you think is at Nanyaksa?
- (Chayoung) Now, now…
- (Hongsik) There was a click, right?
No, I, I, yes, I
(Joosung)
This hard! Shoes crackle!
(Chayoung)
Uh, now, if you put your hands on it
Close your eyes and feel it
(Hongsik)
No, no
The sound came from a temple.
(Joosung)
No, like this…
(Chayoung)
Huh? child
[nervous music]
Where are you going to feel the gold?
[moktak sound effect]
Why did you come back?
(Hongsik)
Hey, what are they doing now?
[Interesting music]
(Vincenzo)
I am doing 108 times.
(Hongsik)
Suddenly?
108 times? Why, why?
To get rid of greed and selfishness.
(Joosung)
wooden avalokitesvara bodhisattva
[moktak sound effect]
(Vincenzo)
wooden avalokitesvara bodhisattva
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
We have to finish 108 times.
Could you please go back now?
[moktak sound effect]
[Embarrassed groan]
(Chayoung)
Come on, everyone go out
Let's find the gold in our hearts
- (President Cho) Attorney
- (Vincenzo) Yes
(President Cho)
Looks like something big has happened
(Vincenzo)
What's going on?
(President Cho)
In the secret room earlier
It looks like they put in an eye recognition device.
[moktak sound effect]
What does that mean?
My clothes earlier
You put it in a secret room, right?
Yes, why?
There was a device inside the clothes
[sigh]
[Exciting music]
Ah
[Emphasized sound effect]
(Vincenzo)
Hey!
Hey, you!
(President Cho)
You?
- (Vincenzo) You, Mr.
- (President Cho) Mr.?
[Vincenzo’s Lament]
(President Cho)
The lawyer put the clothes in.
Why are you putting that on your clothes?
So where do you put it?
Well, lol
Do you carry that?
There isn't just one recognition device, right?
[Laugh together]
It's one
(President Cho)
yes on this earth
There is only one in this universe!
hey!
(President Cho)
'Hey' again
[Vincenzo sobs]
[Ancient music]
(President Cho)
This building really has to come down now
gold can be taken out
My heart right now
It seems to be falling apart
[Vincenzo and President Cho weep]
What's going on?
(Vincenzo)
Oh, pour!
After doing 108 times
I felt the energy of Buddha in my heart.
[wailing]
[Vincenzo sobs]
This is my first time seeing Goseong’s enlightenment.
head monk
If I realize this twice, my eardrums will burst.
(Vincenzo)
Oh, pour!
[sigh]
What on earth do you think of people?
(Vincenzo)
About me
I call you my family
I was thinking
so far we
We've done a lot of things together
It will continue to be like that.
Yes, isn't it?
(people)
yes
Then like that...
Is it okay to be suspicious of people or not?
(people)
No way
I, everyone
I just thought you trusted me...
[Sobbing]
[Lonely music]
[Vincenzo sobs]
(Vincenzo)
Manager
[Chayoung sighs]
You really do it so much
(Chayoung)
How much we care for you
[Jusung hits the wall]
sorry
We were too careless.
Definitely a prize
They say they will give you 20 million won
(Heesu)
It's so ridiculous and strange
(Vincenzo)
Yes, 20 million won
20 million won is a lot of money, but
[sniffles]
One of the things I invested in stocks
It exploded unexpectedly
I wanted to share it with you!
What stocks have you invested in?
- (in advance) Hey, Mr. Lee
- (Yeonjin) Why are you really like that?
(Vincenzo)
Anyway, I'm very disappointed.
[dramatic music]
To relieve my mind
I think it will take some time.
[Pulls out a tissue]
It will take quite a long time for me too
I think it will heal
[Vincenzo sobs]
[Cheolwook takes a breath]
As a representative of the Plaza people, I
I would like to apologize
[sniffling]
Done
Let's go first.
[Vincenzo sniffs]
(Yeonjin)
Oh, sorry.
[Vincenzo sobs]
[Yeonjin sighs]
[The door slams shut]
[Sunam’s sigh]
(Seokdo)
Now, okay?
Hey, I solved everything.
Let's go to the hot springs
(Yeonjin)
Oh, is the hot spring a problem now?
Our lawyer Vincenzo was very angry.
(Hongsik)
Come on, together
Find the gold in your heart
I guess I'm ready to go
[sniffling]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[Vincenzo laughs slightly]
[Chayoung’s excited breathing]
[Vincenzo clicks his tongue]
(Chayoung)
When I opened it, was everything really there?
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
[Interesting music]
[Chayoung’s elasticity]
Even gold and guillotine files?
yes
[Chayoung cheers]
(Vincenzo)
There is even a large golden Buddha.
[Joosung’s laughter]
(Chayoung)
Oh my, golden Buddha!
[Joosung groans in pain]
(Joosung)
It hurts so much, it hurts so much, but I’m so happy!
[Chayoung cheers]
Manager!
[laughter]
(Chayoung)
Well done, well done, very well done
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
Well done, well done, well done, well done
Okay, let's see, this time.
I can go on a cherry blossom tour.
Aha
Let's open it again then
(Joosung)
Let's open it again
[Laugh together]
Let's open it again, let's open it again
(Vincenzo)
I can't open it anymore
(Joosung)
I can't open it
(Chayoung)
ok
(Joosung)
If you can't open it...
[Vincenzo sobs]
[dramatic music]
(Vincenzo)
[Sobbing]
I can't open it now
[Jusung falls down]
(Chayoung)
Oh, Secretary!
[Meaningful music]
(Junwoo)
I expected it, but everyone is really shameless.
have no shame
[smiling slightly]
As long as it isn't revealed
I don't think it's shameful
They are humans
[laughter]
(Myunghee)
Far from being ashamed
I received a very fair price.
will think
This is enough
Law, media, National Assembly, government, and intelligence agencies
Everything will be covered, right?
Yes, I think that's enough
[Junwoo’s powerful moans]
Are you upset because I suddenly became like this today?
no, no
Of course, you should take the position of chairman.
(Chinese book)
I, uh…
I'll just do my best to help.
(Junwoo)
no
Not working hard is for my own good.
(Chinese book)
Yes, I understand, brother.
Well, since we are all here today,
[Laughs slightly]
(Seunghyuk)
I have one thing to tell you
I don't know if you've heard of it
It's called a guillotine file.
[nervous music]
Representative Han
You can't keep hiding it, lawyer.
What is it, a guillotine file?
(Seunghyuk)
Ah, that
It's a bit of a long story.
Uh, what is that?
Let's go back a few years
[Chayoung’s crazy laughter]
[sigh]
[Lonely music]
(Chayoung)
So now you can't get anything out.
Gold guillotine file too
Gold Buddha too
Look at the house too
Take a look at the car too
Look at stocks too...
I saw it
Moreover, the business partner whom I trusted with utmost confidence was
I'm a secret foreign security intelligence agent.
(Chayoung)
That's not enough
You're a traitor
[laughter]
It's just the worst peak.
[Chayoung sighs]
[Interesting music]
Is there another way?
It's a consigliere.
Brain, Trickster
There is none
There isn't any
Except tearing down this building.
There's no way
[Bicycle bell rings]
Cheetah, we just
Will I be crushed to death while hugging gold?
Even just for a moment?
Just live, whatever.
(Chayoung)
Since when was gold mine?
People need to know fractions
[Chayoung sobs]
[Sobbing]
my gold!
- (Chayoung) My gold, my gold
- (Vincenzo) Stop…
(Joosung)
Do…
My Precious!
(Vincenzo)
Manager, change…
[Chayoung and Joosung sob]
Ah, lawyer.
[Meaningful music]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
the file
How fatal is it to our barbell?
I don't know the details
The whole group may be shaken
No, what the heck
How long is it?
(Myunghee)
From what I heard at the time
Even the private life of the former chairman
They say it's in it
The auction ended well today, then.
Those people
Isn't everything solvable?
As expected
More than half of the people gathered today
It should be in the guillotine file.
(Junwoo)
[screaming]
What the…
Then let's share that.
It's no use, right?
That's not it
please wait
(Chinese book)
no
Is there any way to find it right away? huh?
[Clears cough]
Why is everyone so incompetent, Mr.
sorry
It's currently hard to find
(Junwoo)
1 billion
Even if it costs 10 billion, I will find it.
Okay
We will rely on the best experts
(Junwoo)
Okay
(Seunghyuk)
Oh my, hey
[Seunghyuk hums]
[Seunghyuk’s surprised groan]
until there is a solution
I told you not to tell me, right?
No, this
Because there doesn't seem to be a solution
That's what I said.
(Seunghyuk)
And if you miss the timing,
It really hurts more.
[heavy music]
Hey
Seunghyuk Han
Yes, senior
Bring the guillotine file to Chairman Jang Han-seok.
Do you want me to swear allegiance?
What do you mean by that?
Or what, is it a bit like a leg of lamb?
If you get caught with Jang Han-seo,
Because I'm going to die
Oh my, why are you doing this to me again?
Did you finish writing the essay?
(Myunghee)
Seunghyuk
(Seunghyuk)
Huh?
If you cross your legs incorrectly
You know this crotch tear, right?
If the tear occurs and excessive bleeding occurs,
Jordan River by high-speed motorboat
You can cross, right?
(Seunghyuk)
Oh, really, I
older sister
I'm Han Seunghyuk
If only I lived like that
I didn't make it this far
We've come this far
From now on, it's a big problem
Oh my, I really
[Ancient music]
(Seunghyuk)
Ah, my sister.
I'm a really serious person
I know it, tsk
And so scary again
You look at me again, I
I'm thick, huh?
I will always protect my sister
I am deeply...
Oh, I'm a little busy, I have to go quickly.
Uh, honey… You're not calling?
[Seunghyuk’s urgent groan]
Oh my, he did that
If the grim reaper really follows you
Say hello to me
[The bereaved family weeps]
-Bring (the bowl)
- (Union Member 1) What is it, Mr. Lee!
[Meaningful music]
[Noisy]
(Union member 1 on TV)
Nam Shin-bae, you bastard!
(Union member 2 on TV)
Chairman!
(Bereaved family)
Jiwon is Dad!
[People on TV are noisy]
[Prosecutor Jeong’s sigh]
(Vincenzo)
What are they doing?
The body of the deceased Babel Chemical Union Chairman
(Prosecutor Jeong)
The union members are stealing it.
I'm trying to prevent you from holding a union meeting.
[heavy music]
[Puts down the remote control]
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
These are the services provided to Geumga Plaza.
Gurkha double sword tattoo
Oh, I heard about it.
Are you saying they are very cruel?
(Chayoung)
Write, but
Even the union was dispatched?
(Prosecutor Jeong)
More than half of the union members
These are services like that.
(Vincenzo)
But what does the union leader mean by that?
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Oh, the union leader literally
All Babel Chemical union members pay
It's a very big funeral.
Naturally revealed to the media
Union members also
You will receive stronger stimulation.
In short, I am afraid that union members will become mentally stronger.
They won't let you have a funeral.
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Woosang said I summoned Chairman Jang Han-seok.
I would expect it to be put on hold.
the most powerful witness
Because the union president is dead.
Then we have to break expectations.
Summon it away
Substantial evidence is lacking
(Prosecutor Jeong)
beyond imagination
There has been too much interference with the investigation.
So the union president's testimony
It was really important
Did Attorney Choi Myung-hee investigate?
Of course I did it
(Prosecutor Jeong)
It was like that even when I was in office.
Do you get angry when you have to work while seeing blood?
Do you drive the horse while you're at it?
Where there is no evidence
It's a commotion!
(Prosecutor Jeong)
The lawyer is not the one to leave evidence.
But aren't you really blindfolded?
As soon as we have a meal together
Is the chairman going to scream!
It was the drunk driver who sent the scream!
(Myunghee)
These days
I guess coincidence is also grounds for prosecution?
Coincidence?
Why to the lawyer
Are there always only elaborate coincidences?
Without even being able to prove it
Just because you open your mouth doesn't mean you're a prosecutor!
If you feel like working like that,
Go and become a shaman!
[Meaningful music]
[Chayoung’s disgusted moans]
(Chayoung)
Just by hearing it, Myunghee Choi
It looks like it's in 8K high definition
Ugh, I really don't want to see this, mr, tsk.
In this situation, even if Chairman Jang is summoned,
I don't think it will have much effect.
That's expected
If it falls apart from the beginning
(Chayoung)
The remaining five cases to be prosecuted
It will collapse one after another
(Vincenzo)
Well, it's a word kids use, but
Isn’t the first bread important?
in our own way
Let's collect the evidence
As a prosecutor, I am so embarrassed.
Please
[Chayoung sighs]
(Chayoung)
The union issue at all affiliates of Babel is
person directly subordinate to the chairman
It is managed by the vision planning team.
[Exciting music]
It won't be easy
Loyalty is very high.
That's right, these loyalists
Going to jail
He wasn't scared at all
Then, after all, it’s better than prison
I need to find something that scares me more.
Rather than a vision planning team
The first step is to break up the union.
It will get better
(Joosung)
After investigating
They are bastards beyond imagination.
The vision planning team
Leading those bastards
First, let’s start with the union leader, Eoyong.
[Vincenzo and Chayoung’s refreshing moans]
(Chayoung)
Now, let’s find out the king of bastards.
[Strengthening]
Let's go
(Vincenzo)
Oh my, oh my
[Joosung’s powerful moans]
(Joosung)
No, why did you leave the office?
He said we should have a meeting somewhere like this.
(Vincenzo)
So, what I'm saying is
Oh, please hold on to me
(Joosung)
I'll help you
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[sniffles]
Tried to have a gambling meeting, tsk
[dark music]
[Puts down the glass]
(Vincenzo)
Don't ever point a gun at me again
Because I thought of you as a true friend all along.
This time I'll just skip it.
I'm sorry it happened this way
I also have a business relationship
I have never dealt with a lawyer before.
Because you are the savior of my life
I accept it wholeheartedly.
Just like we've done so far
keep helping me
Only then can we find a solution.
[Puts down the glass]
[President Cho sighs]
[The door swings shut]
[Music that heightens the mood]
Are you here?
(Seunghyuk)
sorry
Ah, it's been a while since I drove a car.
The road is confusing
(Chinese book)
i
You did everything you were told.
But what is this!
[Interesting music]
Well, nothing worked out well!
So just shoot at that time
If you do it correctly
This is it...
It's a shotgun
Who says you'll die even if you just shoot it casually?
who is this!
sorry
Now you're killing me
It's just a matter of time
Take it for a while and then just
Well, I'm just going to kill him.
Chairman Jang Han-seok
I will never be able to do that.
Chairman, you are family.
[sigh]
Representative Han, did you forget everything?
(Seunghyuk)
yes?
My brother is also my father
He sent it with his own hand.
(Seunghyuk)
Ah, that's right
(Chinese book)
‘Oh, that’s right’?
(Seunghyuk)
So the Chairman is the last one left.
Aren’t you the only family?
Let's believe so, let's be positive
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
[Hanseo’s thinking groan]
believe it
I really believe it
Let's say you're lucky to survive.
Even if I'm alive
Now!
There's nothing I can do
nothing, nothing
(Seunghyuk)
Is there any? Is there any?
Well, isn't there something there?
Think of something...
[Snaps fingers]
Ah, that!
Take this opportunity to rest
[dark music]
And become even more stupid
Oh, what are you saying?
(Seunghyuk)
First, we need to reassure Chairman Jang Han-seok.
The Chairman never
That I'm not the person to do anything else
I have to show it.
Think back to history
To avoid the oppression of the Andong Kim clan, huh?
Pretending to be a fool
Heungseon Daewongun, who commanded the world
Heungseon, I have a father, Gojong.
I know, I know
(Seunghyuk)
So, like Heungseon, yes?
[Meaningful music]
Just be an asshole
Absolutely!
(Chinese book)
These bastards, the country’s green peak is a breeze
Eating it all up
There's nothing to do straight, nothing to do
Hey, what is it?
This bastard, I just said
Didn’t I tell you to buy me a cheeseburger?
(Detective 1)
Is the lawyer here?
(Myunghee)
What's going on?
[Hanseo is noisy]
(Detective 1)
I was brought in for assaulting an employee at a bar.
It keeps doing that.
(Detective 2)
For now, reporters have been blocked.
Let's take him quickly.
(Chinese book)
Ah, hey
Let it go, let it go, you bastard
Let it go!
Hey, I'll give you some pocket money.
Those bastards were the first to be thrown in.
I give you pocket money, come on, take it.
Take it! 거지새끼들아, 씨
회장님
(한서)
최 변, 하, 최 변
최 변 잘 왔어요
[의미심장한 음악]
여기 있는 새끼들
경찰이고 뭐고 다 고소해
다 처넣어, 씨!
(Chayoung)
He's not even an idol
Very friendly, indeed
(Joosung)
Even overseas, people call me a handsome CEO.
[Joosung’s laughter]
[Chayoung’s exasperated groan]
Oh my gosh, I'm so excited
[Mouse click sound]
This is not an article
Is this a submission to the Spring Literary Contest?
[Mouse click sound]
Anyway, we achieved our goal.
(Vincenzo)
Finally in front of the public tomorrow, huh?
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
Has Prosecutor Jeong set an invitation date?
[Seunghyuk’s surprised groan]
On suspicion of labor union breakdown
Are you subpoenaing and investigating?
[Puts the kettle down]
Chairman Jang Han-seok?
As if to show off, the president’s inauguration ceremony
the very next day
[sigh]
(Seunghyuk)
No, no, we don't think so.
It was folding.
No, the union president is also dead.
There won't be any evidence?
Well, it's probably one of two things.
Either I was embarrassed to close it, or
There really is something
(Seunghyuk)
Ah, the union president is just that.
Didn’t they just let him die without any countermeasures?
Do you blame me?
[Laughing]
What kind of resentment am I holding on to?
I just don't want things to go wrong
I'm doing it because I'm worried.
[clattering down the glass]
Nothing else matters
[Meaningful music]
Vision Planning Team All you need to do is prevent search and seizure
Well, unless there is solid evidence.
There's no warrant.
The position of Chief Prosecutor Hwang is also the same.
I'm summoning you, so I guess I'll have to take a picture.
Should we stop by the store in the morning?
[Junwoo sighs]
Knowing clearly that it was my inauguration day
Get into an accident
[Shameless sigh]
I'm sorry, brother, I
(Chinese book)
It feels so good, oh
Because I drink too much
[Embarrassed laughter]
please forgive me
[Junwoo laughs]
(Junwoo)
What is forgiveness
For the first time in a while, I really like how you look like yourself
You have to live like that often
Ah, I guess I'm like this
Tsk, living recklessly
That seems correct, yes
[Laughing]
I feel at ease
(Junwoo)
Now
It's a symbol that we brothers are one
[Junwoo laughs]
Never betray each other
Be the best at barbelling
[Junwoo sighs]
If Babel fails, the country will fail.
We need to make people think
Yes, brother
[Junwoo laughs slightly]
[Junwoo sighs]
Ah
Did I tell you?
The reason I passed on the hunting ground job
[nervous music]
[Embarrassed groan]
That…
it was just a real accident
Brother, I
No, how can I
That doesn't make any sense...
(Junwoo)
you need to be alive
[shaking breathing]
When you die, who will go to jail instead of me?
If I become the chairman and have to go to jail
You should go instead
Isn't it?
yes
Yes, brother, yes
Yes, I
I'm willing to go
Yes, brother
I am confident that I will do well in that prison cell.
(Chinese book)
yes, yes
Don't worry, brother, I
I will do anything for you, brother.
(Junwoo)
As expected, my younger brother
Let's go to the inauguration ceremony
[sigh]
[Meaningful music]
[Music that heightens the mood]
"Babel"
[Camera shutter sounds repeatedly]
(Employee 1)
come this way
[Junwoo clears his throat]
(Seunghyuk)
Hey, hey, hey, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute
Spread your shoulders
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
- (Host) From today, our Babel
- (Seunghyuk) Smile a little, okay?
- (Host) We will be reborn
- (Seunghyuk) Smile, you’re pretty when you smile
(Moderator)
With Chairman Jang Han-seok
[nervous music]
[Junwoo’s nervous breathing]
This makes me nervous in its own way
(Junwoo)
Now, photo
(Chinese book)
[Laughing]
yes
(Employee 2)
Let's start the event now
Please go up
(Myunghee)
Now really
You become the leader of Babel.
(Chinese book)
Congratulations, Mr. Chairman.
Until now, my younger brother
Thanks to good management, huh?
(Seunghyuk)
Chairman, I think you should go up.
Let's go
[Camera shutter sounds repeatedly]
Okay, let's go.
Chairman Jang Han-seok
“Babel Group”
[bright music]
(Vincenzo)
Ah, this cheese
[Chayoung and Joosung’s savoring moans]
[Savoring moans]
It's delicious anytime you eat at this place
(Vincenzo)
Babel Group Vision Planning Team
Have you never been searched and seized?
I didn't get a warrant.
Due to lack of explanation of the facts of the charge.
That's why Prosecutor Jeong is even more upset.
I have to shake it off from there.
(Joosung)
All you have to do is rob them and the union will collapse.
Documents of various illegal activities
It would come rushing out.
(Vincenzo)
We went to the union as planned.
Just dig a trap
Did you find out about the union president?
[Exciting music]
(Joosung)
Yes, originally
He was the right-hand man of the deceased union president.
Betrayal in a moment
I went over to the company.
It is an icon of complete betrayal.
[Vincenzo’s groan of approval]
(Chayoung)
Well, I guess I was 100% bought off.
(Joosung)
But it's not just a passing thing.
The union president who was like a brother to me
They even accused me of false information.
Hey, you're such a traitor.
Babel Group Vision Planning Team Leader
What kind of person are you?
(Team Leader Park)
Attorney Park, Attorney Yoon
It's difficult if you do things so sloppily.
(Chayoung)
Known for being perfect and thorough.
[Team Leader Park speaks]
Lawyers even after coming to idols
I stir-fried it a lot.
They say things are handled sloppyly.
[Team Leader Park’s angry groan]
(Chinese book)
Isn't there something delicious?
[Hanseo speaks]
(Team Leader Park)
Hello, Chairman.
Ah, Team Leader Park, yes.
(Chinese book)
Hey, order three quick, quick.
(Bodyguard 1)
yes, i understand
(Chayoung)
And above all, loyalty
It's almost like a golden retriever.
(Vincenzo)
As much as the traitor and the loyal
causing good chemical reactions
There is no between
How do those two chemically react?
Will I wake up well?
What the faithful fear most
The owner's distrust
[Exciting music]
What the owner is most worried about
It's someone's betrayal
Preventing that betrayal
It's the biggest duty of a loyal person.
(Chayoung)
The weakness of the faithful is
It is exposed when betrayal occurs.
I'm just taking advantage of that timing.
(Joosung)
Where is this?
Isn’t that something they teach at academies?
Pay 300,000 per month
I will teach you with attributes.
Um, no, I need to get 40 a month.
(Joosung)
Done
Would you like to learn Pilates with that money?
Tomorrow is the day to recall Chairman Jang, right?
Yes, for today
Let’s deal with the betrayal icon first.
[Interesting music]
[Strong moan]
[Car door slams shut]
[Car remote control operation sound]
[takes a breath]
[Interesting music stops]
child
[breathe]
[Interesting music]
[The spirit of worship]
[nervous music]
[Shinbae’s surprised groan]
(New Bae)
What is it
[Scream of God]
Go away, go away
[Cheolwook’s powerful moans]
Who is it? Go away, save people!
[Scream of God]
[Cheolwook’s powerful moans]
[Emphasized sound effect]
Double swords faction?
Boy, I was surprised.
Hey, really
[Cheolwook groans in pain]
Ssanggeompa, our family
- (Cheolwook) Yes
- (Bae) No.
But what are you doing here?
[Cheolwook clears his throat]
(Cheolwook)
When you rap
You just need to remember two things
(New Bae)
yes?
(Cheolwook)
♪ Drumming and headbutting ♪
♪ Drumming, headbutting, drumming, headbutting ♪
[Drum sound effect]
[Laughing]
Ah
(together)
♪ Drumming, headbutting, drumming, headbutting ♪
♪ Drumming and headbutting ♪
(Cheolwook)
[Cheolwook’s heavy breathing]
(New Bae)
headbutt
[Shinbae falls down]
[Crying all night]
[dark music]
[Shinbae’s labored groans]
[A slushy sound is heard]
[groans with difficulty]
[Shinbae’s labored groans]
(New Bae)
What is this
(Joosung)
But is this cement that hardens quickly?
Why doesn't it harden so quickly?
(Sinbae and Ki-seok)
- Hey there.
- Didn't I order something wrong on the Internet?
here
(Cheolwook)
It takes 3 hours to harden
I know what kind of chocolate this is
Hey!
(Vincenzo)
If you're going to hang it on cement and throw it
Isn’t the sea better than a reservoir?
(Chayoung)
That's right, the sea
Even sharks eat and eat, so it’s clean.
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
Hey, to me
Why are you doing this now, yes?
(New Bae)
Ssanggeompa, we are the same family.
(Chayoung)
Wow
[Shinbae’s surprised groan]
You sound like a family member.
Why are we your family?
No, but why is the woman here…
[Shinbae’s surprised groan]
(Chayoung)
Is there a law that says women shouldn’t do things like this?
Gender sensitivity is down, this bastard
sorry
No, but
I think there's some misunderstanding.
(New Bae)
I did nothing wrong
(Kiseok)
You, Lee!
[Interesting music]
The real unions are on the side of the company.
You just bullied me!
(Joosung)
Union officials lied
They said they embezzled public funds.
You said you sexually harassed me!
(Chayoung)
Because of you, I am a union official.
I heard one person committed suicide?
[Vincenzo’s elasticity]
It's so unfair
(Cheolwook)
If I wasn't a true martial artist
You'd be folded like a flip phone
[Cheolwook claps his hands]
Are you a dancer?
[Interesting music stops]
It's not that kind of martial arts!
(Kiseok)
If you were born during the Japanese colonial period
This bastard, this
[Interesting music]
This is a complete stooge, huh?
Is it noticeable?
My grandfather was pro-Japanese.
(Chayoung)
Are you an icon of betrayal from generation to generation?
(Joosung)
Wow, everything has solidified!
[Cheolwook’s laughter]
(New Bae)
What?
- (Shinbae) No way
- (Cheolwook) Finally!
- (Vincenzo) Is it all set?
- (Juseong) It’s all hardened, it’s hard.
No, no
(Vincenzo)
no personal feelings
'Cause we do what we're told
Oh, sleep, wait a minute, wait a minute
(New Bae)
No, but who on earth ordered it?
(Chayoung)
It's obvious, whatever
You have no use for it anymore
It's not like that
Babel these two bastards, really, sir.
(Cheolwook)
Come on!
Now, shall we slowly put it together?
- yes?
- (Vincenzo) Come on, drag him away.
(New Bae)
No, no, wait a minute.
[Exciting music]
Oh, this, what are you doing?
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute
[Noisy]
Just a moment, please help me, please help me
I'll give you anything
I will do whatever I ask.
(Joosung)
If you have money, how much money do you have? That’s it!
(New Bae)
No, no, you can make it!
I turn all my heads
I'll make it happen somehow
(Vincenzo)
If you think about it, well
Tie up the body and the barrel quickly.
(New Bae)
Oh no, don't touch me anywhere
Oh, that's real cement!
Don't do it, uh, why are you like this?
- (Joosung) One, two, three
- (Sinbae) Please save me
[Scream of God]
(Cheolwook)
Fighting
(New Bae)
Hey, don't do this, hey, hey
Uh, please help me
Is there anyone?
Lord!
Oh, I'm dying!
- (Joosung) Hey, hey!
- (Cheolwook) Tie it up!
[The priest sings a hymn]
(together)
one, two, three
(Cheolwook)
Tied up, Mr.
(Chayoung)
Wait!
[Crying all night]
Have you received any orders from head office?
What should the union over there do?
Sure, yeah
It comes to your email every morning
- (Chayoung) Are you sure?
- (New Bae) Yes
Is it true?
- Yes
- (Chayoung) Okay
(Chayoung)
Everyone gather together for a moment
(together)
One, two, hey!
[Interesting music]
Those bastards, that
(New Bae)
Save people, save people!
[Shinbae’s surprised groan]
(Chayoung)
You said you would do everything you asked, right?
Is there any
[Shinbae sniffles]
(Chayoung)
Call!
[Shinbae’s surprised groan]
[God's laughter]
(New Bae)
yes
[God's laughter]
What? 2 billion?
Yes, 2 billion
(New Bae)
Don't pay taxes
[dark music]
You know who I am now
Are you being picky?
[God's laughter]
Are you flirting?
Yeah, I'm a bitch.
So are you Dongbaek?
[Laugh together]
Hey, you told me to kill you, right?
What are you talking about?
(New Bae)
I don't need it all
Until tomorrow, huh?
Bring 2 billion in cash right now
Otherwise I
Emails and orders received from the vision planning team
All kinds of corruption!
Starting with you, Team Leader Park.
Everything will be revealed
Everything!
[Sighing]
Chairman, please calm down for now.
talk to me
(New Bae)
no
There's no need for conversation
Call me when the money's ready, hang up
[People's exclamations and laughter]
(Cheolwook)
Eat, eat
Oh, eat it, it’s delicious.
Wow, it's great
(together)
Naughty, naughty, naughty
Chairman, this bastard.
(Vincenzo)
I told you this before, right?
More if you let me go
I can get it
My client
You kept your promise like a sword.
What is it?
[Meaningful music]
(Vincenzo)
Babel Group Vision Planning Team
Sent to the union president
This is an order document to suppress the union.
No, how could this...
(Chayoung)
If the evidence is this much
Vision Planning Team Search and Seizure Warrant
You can get it, right?
[Prosecutor Jeong passes over documents]
(Prosecutor Jeong)
yes
I think it's possible with this much content.
There is one condition before search and seizure.
[intense music]
[Intense sound effect]
[Cheolwook’s savoring moans]
(together)
salty
(Chayoung)
A
[Cheolwook’s laughter]
I'm not really a lawyer
I think I'm a gangster
(Kiseok)
Me too, me too, me too
Something like, ah, ah, adrenaline
It feels like it's just gushing out.
I went to Italy with my lawyer.
- (Chayoung) Shall we do consiglieri?
- (Vincenzo) Eat.
(Cheol-wook and Joo-seong)
- Me, me, me, me, me, me, me
- Me too, me too, I really am
(Chayoung)
Oh, okay, okay, let's go together.
[People respond]
Yes, call!
You seem to have talent for the mafia, right?
Enjoy
(Kiseok)
In terms of talent, I guess...
Oh, I'm from
[Chayoung and Vincenzo groan in agreement]
(Chayoung)
That's right, yeah
[laughter]
When everyone comes to Italy later
Would you like to sprinkle some pig blood?
[Cheolwook chuckles]
[Interesting music]
Pig blood?
[Clears cough]
What is that again?
existed until the 1960s
Our family has our own way
The opposing family boss has changed
party day
To show off our power
Sprinkle pig blood on the opposing boss.
It means don't attack me.
[Kiseok’s disgusted moans]
(Kiseok)
Well, that's a bit weird, what's the smell like?
[Cheolwook responds]
I hate it too
It's so barbaric.
but i miss you
It's a complete visual explosion.
[Vincenzo laughs slightly]
(Joosung)
I don't like it either
Why bother with this delicious food?
[elegant music]
(Vincenzo)
Now
Eat this and grow fast
Let me get some good sleep too, okay?
[Dove cries]
Do you even understand what people are saying?
huh?
[Dove cries]
[Laughs]
If you understand what I'm saying
Be sure to repay the favor later, okay?
Because I fed them like this
Okay?
[laughter]
eat
(Vincenzo)
yes
[Camera shutter sounds repeatedly]
[Car door slams shut]
[Meaningful music]
(Reporter 1)
Please tell us your thoughts.
(Junwoo)
Without any doubt
I will faithfully participate in the investigation.
And the people
As a trustworthy company
I will leap forward again
(Reporter 2)
He was summoned as soon as he took office as president.
How are you feeling?
(Reporter 3)
Do you deny the allegations?
(Reporter 4)
Illegal union breakdown...
(Anchor on TV)
This is breaking news that just came in.
[nervous music]
Babel Group Chairman Jang Han-seok
Italy's finest handmade suits
There is news that he appeared wearing a bralo.
This prosecution's summons investigation
What do you think?
(panel)
About this talented businessman
A prosecutor's fault
I think it's taming
[Junwoo speaks on TV]
(anchor)
Aha
- (Panel) It’s very outdated.
- (Anchor) Yes
- (Panel) Look at Chairman Lee and Jang Han-seok.
(panel)
So smart and charismatic
Have you ever seen a businessman?
(anchor)
yes
(panel)
And how handsome is he?
(anchor)
A smart and charismatic handsome businessman
Add it here
Exercise, yes?
shooting
Even painting skills
[The anchor in the video continues speaking]
(Joosung)
Oh my, it’s so torn down.
It will wear out and disappear.
I try so hard to suck it up
All the news is like this
It's all fake, it's all crap
The development of media and the transmission of truth
There's no correlation.
Me too until recently
Because there was a lot of press.
(Joosung)
Actually
Fooling people thanks to the internet
It's a great time
So what I believe on the internet is
There are only two things
date and time
[Chayoung’s sneer]
[Junwoo is humming]
[Myunghee’s sigh]
[Junwoo laughs slightly]
(Vincenzo)
There is one condition before search and seizure.
[Meaningful music]
(Prosecutor Jeong)
What are the conditions?
Seizure and search information to Idol and Babel
Spill it in advance
Yes?
(Chayoung)
Have the vision planning team steal data
I'm making it
Then aren’t we empty-handed?
(Vincenzo)
Our goal is
It's not about securing evidence of union suppression.
(Vincenzo)
Instructions to destroy the union
Chairman Jang himself made the decision.
It proves it.
[Myunghee keeps snapping her fingers]
(Myunghee)
May I make a bet?
7pm tonight
Our Chairman Jang
against young leaders
There is a lecture
In ‘I leave here before that’
[Snaps fingers]
I'll bet you 10,000 won
[laughter]
oh
Prosecutor Woori Jeong
The jokes have increased a bit, huh?
Thank you Berry Much
But why did you call me and not say anything?
order to break up the union
The chairman made the decision, right?
(Prosecutor Jeong)
From Idol’s lawyer days.
child
[Junwoo’s laughter]
(Myunghee)
I've never been like that
Oh, that's right, um
Would you like some food?
(Myunghee)
Let's eat
it's ok here
Of course
[sigh]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Team Leader Park)
Yes, Attorney Park.
yes
Yes?
[nervous music]
(Team Leader Park)
Come on, quickly.
[Clapping hands]
quickly
move fast
No time to shred
First, organize everything you have.
Put it in this assistant manager’s car
- (Team Leader Park) Assistant Manager Lee, move quickly.
- Yes!
Come on, come on!
[People are noisy]
Hello, elevator number 2.
This is elevator number 2.
[Laugh together]
(Security Manager)
Wait!
I don't think it's our employees.
What are you guys?
If you don't reveal your affiliation, I'll report you to the police.
I live in Wangsimni
It's called Namjuseong...
[Music that heightens tension]
I was dispatched based on a tip from my superiors.
To protect the vision planning team
Isn’t this an impersonation?
(Kiseok)
Then call and ask
If it's true, you should interfere with official duties!
Ooh, we are the Wangsimni branch!
That's right, newbie
If you come to Wangsimni, you will be scolded!
[Elevator sound]
"Guard
Babel Group"
Could you please press the basement level?
Are you going to the 3rd floor underground?
[Cheolwook’s laughter]
Did you have a sudden poop?
Why is it going so fast?
Are you very busy?
(Assistant Manager Lee)
Oh no
(Chayoung)
What are you hiding? Show us too
(Cheolwook)
Show me, show me
- (Assistant Manager Lee) It’s not a big deal.
- (Cheolwook) What is it?
(Cheolwook)
Oh my, what did I hear so much about?
[Chayoung’s surprised gasp]
(Vincenzo and Cheolwook)
- What?
- Look at this, this is heavy, this.
- (Vincenzo) What is this?
- (Cheolwook) I will help you, I
[intense music]
No, it's not heavy at all
I can do it alone
(Cheolwook)
Wow, this is heavy. This?
[Assistant Manager Lee’s embarrassed groan]
How did you run with this by yourself?
(Cheolwook and Chayoung)
Oh my
(Cheolwook)
Uh, it's okay, it's okay
It's okay, it's okay, try 'our baby'
(Anchor on TV)
What Chairman Jang Han-seok wore today
Reaction to the Bralo suit
It's very hot
Real-time search rankings now
Take first place...
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Have some
(Myunghee)
Do some work, Prosecutor Jeong.
Or just let it go
[Clears cough]
I will eat well
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Meaningful music]
(Team Leader Park)
Vision Planning Team Search and Seizure Warrant Issued
Fortunately, we were informed first and action was taken.
[Junwoo’s laughter]
You held me back like this, huh?
(Myunghee)
Let’s talk about the vision planning team.
If you can, give it a try.
I don't know what will come out
[Myunghee’s laughter]
(Junwoo)
Let me ask you one question, prosecutor.
An honest prosecutor who follows the law well.
Why did you join hands with the mafia?
I didn't join hands with the mafia.
It's about following trends.
What?
The trend of the times is
Not forgiveness and harmony
Because it is separated from the eradication.
[Laugh together]
[Junwoo’s laughter and applause]
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Oh, you said there was a lecture, right?
Go and have fun talking.
(Myunghee)
Eat a lot
Well, there won't be time to eat.
You should eat well before leaving.
Of course
(Myunghee)
I am tail gomtang
[Junwoo’s savoring moans]
- (Prosecutor Jeong) Tail gomtang?
- (Myunghee) Yes
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Yeah
You ordered it earlier.
[Junwoo’s savoring moans]
(Junwoo)
Add radish radish
(Anchor on TV)
This is breaking news
[Meaningful music plays]
Chairman Jang Han-seok to dinner
I asked for seolleongtang.
They say they added radish radish
Ah, this is a very unusual case.
Chairman Jang Han-seok's kkakdugi added
What does it mean?
(panel on TV)
Ah, to let the outside world know that I am healthy.
It seems like a high-level message.
[surprised moan]
Ah, so
I should have prepared the money a long time ago
(Team Leader Park)
Do you know what kind of data it is?
If it's revealed, you and I will both die!
I don't die
Next, bring 2 billion to the place I told you about.
(New Bae)
you do it yourself
If you break even one thing
I'm going to shoot these documents straight to the prosecutor.
Okay? Boom!
[People's elasticity]
[Interesting music]
(New Bae)
yes, thank you
Did I do well?
Because I did well
Can you give me one chicken leg?
I haven't eaten anything since yesterday
Uh, what should I do?
This is Gangjeong so there are no legs?
Oh, I see.
Then just give me anything.
[Joosung responds]
[God's laughter]
[Humorous sound effects]
[Savoring moans]
What should I do? You haven't eaten it all?
Boy, really
Please give me just one
(New Bae)
Oh, you are so great, really.
A
- (New Bae) Child
- (Kiseok) Fell, fell.
Oh, so childish, really.
(New Bae)
Boy, really, would you do that with what you eat?
No, really
[car horn]
(Stage Manager)
Check the brightness of the monitor over there.
[Staff responds]
And what, there
Check all lights connections
[Meaningful music]
Can I ask you a favor?
(Stage Manager)
Yes?
(Vincenzo)
For a woman I
I want to hold an event
I'll give you enough examples.
(woman)
Oh, it's the chairman!
[People are noisy]
thank you
I'm sorry
[Camera shutter sounds repeatedly]
[Hanseo whistles]
(Chinese book)
Now
Let’s meet today’s protagonist.
My eternal mentor
My older brother
The leader of our Babel Group
This is Chairman Jang Han-seok.
[People cheering]
[Magnificent music plays]
Nice to meet you
Dear future leaders
This is Jang Han-seok
[Exciting music]
[Vincenzo whistles]
(Junwoo)
The future doesn't belong to anyone
[laughter]
The owner is not determined
Instead, whoever catches it first wins.
But if you catch the strange future first
It's a disaster
[People laughing]
Who wrote that comment?
(Junwoo)
In order to have a good future
[Chayoung sighs]
I must have strong confidence in myself now.
And you have to be reckless
(Chayoung)
Um, thank you
(Junwoo)
Babel's recklessness
I'm going to commit it again
Babel Chemicals produces innovative batteries.
In development
When development is completed 2 years later
We plan to enter the electric vehicle market
[People's elasticity]
Leading the future
Babel Motors’ vision
Let's see
[People applauding]
[Rhythmic music plays]
(Shinbae in the video)
What is this? Why is there only 300 million won?
(Team Leader Park in the video)
What I can be flexible about now
This is all I have
(Shinbae in the video)
No, Babel Group’s
[intense music]
Daejeon planning team leader...
- (Executive) It seems wrong.
- (Hanseo) Why me…
(Shinbae in the video)
If this happens, I won’t be able to return the evidence.
(Chinese book)
No, why, ha
Ah, everyone, this is…
[Hinseo’s embarrassed groan]
[Microphone beeps]
Is there no staff here, staff?
- (Security 2) Checking, just a moment.
- (Hanseo) Check it out quickly.
(Bodyguard 2)
Hey, where is the person in charge?
(New Bae)
Those are the documents that suppressed the union.
I heard it's huge?
If you do something stupid, you will be finished.
Me?
Oh, no
(New Bae)
It's me, well, of Babel Chemistry.
Because he is the president of the pants union.
Not to that extent.
Babel's powerhouse
Vision Planning Team Leader, you will be the end!
Because you made it all up
(Team Leader Park in the video)
It's not something I make up.
I just follow the chairman's orders
A person who moves!
(Shinbae in the video)
Oh, that's none of my business.
[People are upset]
[Video sound continues to play]
(assistant director)
Oh, what are you doing now?
Turn it off quickly!
Just touch the button
(Team Leader Park in the video)
I just follow orders
Puppet…
(Chinese book)
The chairman's name was mentioned.
Hurry up, hurry up
Huh?
What are you going to do?
(Team Leader Park in the video)
Well, what am I doing that for?
I don't know
Hey, let's stay calm
It can be resolved through conversation
You said it was caramel popcorn, right?
Oh my
Popcorn is original.
(Shinbae in the video)
If you don't have money, you can tell the chairman.
(Chayoung)
If you were going to live your life the way you wanted, why did you ask?
Lawyer
Instead, I'll show you something fun.
With scenes as vivid as 8K
(Chayoung)
Is there anything else besides that refreshing scene?
You said there was something you wanted to see, right?
[People in the video are noisy]
[People are upset]
(Junwoo)
장한서 회장, 빨리
(한서)
예, 예
[의미심장한 음악]
야, 이거 빨리 끄라고, 새끼야
너희 뭐, 뭐 하냐!
Don't do it, don't take it
Don't take pictures
[Junwoo’s embarrassed laughter]
(Junwoo)
Um…
(Vincenzo)
[Vincenzo snaps his fingers]
[People screaming]
[intense music]
(Chayoung)
Wow, awesome
[Chayoung’s laughter]
Oh my
I feel like a mafia from the 60's
[Vincenzo laughs]
[Chayoung's exclamation and applause]
(Vincenzo)
Feel it to your heart's content
Feeling like a real villain
(Bodyguard 3)
Don't take pictures!
(Guardian 4)
[Meaningful music]
[shaking breathing]
(Vincenzo)
Bravo!
(Chayoung)
- (Vincenzo) Bravo!
- (Chayoung) Encore!
[Chayoung cheers]
[laughter]
[upbeat music]
(Vincenzo)
This is a really big game
Above all, there must be teamwork.
[People’s spirit]
Oh, wait a minute.
inside this building
Why are there so many talented people?
(Vincenzo)
Chairman Jang Han-seok’s paper company
I plugged in the USB.
(Chayoung)
Just this one
Jang Han-seok Can you make dog hair?
(Junwoo)
I need to turn this around
It's really for my brother.
(Chinese book)
Let’s make a place, Vincenzo and I.
(Junwoo)
Kill it quickly, quickly!
[gunshot]
[Director Jeong’s scream]
(Chayoung)
It's truly an unforgettable night.
Subtitle: Kwon Jeong-won